Preliminary Guide to the New Haven Redevelopment Agency Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
New Haven Redevelopment Agency records
1950-2005
1950-1985
MS 1814
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
770.75
Project files, minutes, correspondence, and property records, documenting the work of the New Haven Redevelopment Agency, primarily from the 1950s to the 1980s.
New Haven Redevelopment Agency
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Deposited by the City of New Haven, 2003, 2005.
Biographical / Historical
The New Haven Redevelopment Agency was established in 1950. It directed and oversaw the major redevelopment projects undertaken in New Haven from that time on.
Scope and Contents
Project files, minutes, correspondence, and property records, documenting the work of the New Haven Redevelopment Agency, primarily from the 1950s to the 1980s.
Arrangement
Arranged in twenty-eight series and one addition: I. Administrative. II. Applications are Rehabilitation Loans. III. Capital Projects. IV. Chronological Files. V. City Housing Projects. VI. City of New Haven. VII. Contracts and Agreements. VIII. Demolition/Contracts. IX. Development Administrator's Files, 1980-1985. X. Environmental Impact. XI. Federal Government. XII. Housing Code Compliances. XIII. Litigation, Closed Files. XIV. Office of Land Disposition. XV. Office of Public Information. XVI. Open Space Program. XVII. Printed. XVIII. Projects. XIX. Regional Water Authority. XX. Reuse Parcel Survey Maps. XXI. State of Connecticut. XXII. Taft-Adams. XXIII. Urban Renewal in Other Cities. XXIV. Workable Programs. XXV. Card Files. XXVI. Minutes, 1959-1995. XXVII. Projects, Miscellaneous. XXVIII. Miscellaneous.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
City planning -- Connecticut -- New Haven; Relocation (Housing) -- Connecticut -- New Haven; Urban renewal -- Connecticut -- New Haven -- History -- 20th Century; Urban renewal -- Connecticut -- New Haven; New Haven (Conn.) -- History -- 20th Century; New Haven (Conn.) -- Politics and government -- 20th Century; Lee, Richard C. (Richard Charles), 1916-2003; Logue, Edward J.; New Haven Redevelopment Agency
- Administrative, Series I
  - General (Box 1)
  - Agency members (Box 1)
  - Staff meetings (Box 1)
  - Personnel (Box 1)
  - Pension (Box 1)
  - Pension (Box 2)
  - Management control system (Box 2)
  - Community development (Box 2)
  - Alderman William Rees (Box 2)
  - Articles, comments, editorials (Box 2)
  - Articles (Box 3)
  - Citizens participation in redevelopment (Box 3)
  - Conflict of interest (Box 3)
  - Election campaigns and candidates (Box 3)
  - Agency offices and leases (Box 3)
  - File room (Box 3)
  - Right-to-know (Box 3)
  - Freedom of Information Act (Box 3)
  - Agency financial
    - Annual administrative budgets (Box 3)
    - Annual administrative budgets (Box 4)
    - HUD audit (Box 4)
    - City capital budgets (Box 4)
    - City capital budgets (Box 5–6)
    - City capital budgets (Box 7)
    - Consolidated financing (Box 7)
    - Consolidated financing (Box 8–11)
    - Consolidated financing (Box 12)
  - Agency information
    - Census (Box 12)
    - New Haven Redevelopment Agency annual reports (Box 13)
    - Quarterly reports (Box 14)
    - Publicity (Box 14)
    - Information requests (Box 14)
    - Information requests (Box 15)
    - Requisitions for forms (Box 15)
    - Digestibility report (Box 15)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 15)
  - Office maintenance (Box 15)
  - Office maintenance, contracts (Box 16–18)
  - Subjects
    - Gordon's Plumbing-Harborside-Fonda (Box 19)
    - Energy, employment task force (Box 20)
- Applications for Rehabilitation Loans, Series II
  - Abbadessa-Bonilla (Box 21)
  - Bonito-Cheatham (Box 22)
  - Chieppo-Dixon (Box 23)
  - Dolberry-Fusco (Box 24)
  - Gabriele-Hodge (Box 25)
  - Hoffler-Kuehl (Box 26)
  - Labagnara-Mikuson (Box 27)
  - Miller-O'Sullivan (Box 28)
  - Pabon-Rochelle (Box 29)
  - Rodman-Stowers (Box 30)
  - Straightway-Williams (Box 31)
  - Williams-Zwack (Box 32)
  - 1-169 (Box 32)
  - 171-357 (Box 33)
  - 355-518B (Box 34)
- Capital Projects, Series III
  - Economic Development Administration, general correspondence (Box 35)
  - Sewers by street
    - 01-51-00320 (Box 35)
    - 01-51-00320 (Box 36)
    - 01-51-00320 (Box 37)
  - Parks by site
    - 01-51-00275 (Box 37)
    - 01-51-00275 (Box 38)
    - 01-51-00275 (Box 39)
  - School energy conservation
    - 01-51-00317 (Box 39)
    - 01-51-00317 (Box 40)
  - Public works employment act (Box 41)
  - Emergency Operations Center underground facilities (Box 41)
  - Emergency Operations Center underground facilities (Box 42–43)
  - Bridges, by street name: Grand Avenue-Tomlinson (Box 44)
  - Olin strike (Box 45)
  - Solid waste (Box 45)
  - New Haven Water Company (Box 45)
  - New Haven Water Company (Box 46)
- Chronological Files, Series IV
  - Executive director
    - 1962-1963 (Box 47)
    - 1964-1965 (Box 48)
    - 1966 (Box 49)
    - 1967 (Box 50)
    - 1968 (Box 51)
    - 1969 (Box 52)
    - 1969-1971 (Box 53)
    - 1972 (Box 54)
    - 1973 (Box 55)
    - 1974 (Box 56)
    - 1975 (Box 57)
    - 1976 (Box 58)
    - 1977 (Box 59)
    - 1978 (Box 60–61)
    - 1979 (Box 62–63)
    - 1980-1981 (Box 64)
  - Executive director appointment books
    - 1966-1969, 1971-1977 (Box 65)
    - 1978-1984 (Box 66)
  - Other staff
    - Jan 1976-Nov 1977 (Box 67)
    - Nov 1976-Aug 1977 (Box 68)
    - Sep 1977-Aug 1978 (Box 69)
    - Aug 1978-Dec 1979 (Box 70)
    - Jan 1980-Jan 1982 (Box 71)
- City Housing Projects, Series V
  - Wilmot Road
    - General (Box 72)
    - Acquisitions (Box 73)
    - Capital improvements and contracts (Box 73)
    - Contracts (Box 74)
    - Contracts, disposition (Box 75)
    - Disposition (Box 76)
    - Financial (Box 77)
    - Public hearings, maps, property management (Box 78)
    - Reports, traffic and parking, zoning, housing sites (Box 79)
  - Middletown Avenue housing sites (Box 79)
  - Middletown Avenue housing sites (Box 80)
- City of New Haven, Series VI
  - General, city action program (Box 81)
  - City action program, manpower management, charter revision, controller, pension, city commissions (Box 82)
  - Commission on Equal Opportunity, authorities (Box 83)
  - Board of Alderman (Box 84)
  - Economic Decelopment Commission (Box 84)
  - New Haven Development Corporation (Box 84)
  - Parking Authority (Box 84)
  - Board of Education; Board of Finance (Box 85)
  - Boards, departments
    - Building Department (Box 86)
    - City Plan Department (Box 86)
    - Corporation Counsel (Box 86)
    - Fire Department (Box 86)
    - Health Department (Box 86)
    - Swine Flu Vaccination Program, 1976 (Box 86)
    - Office of Policy Analysis (Box 86)
    - Parks Department (Box 86)
    - Edgewood Park Rowing Course (Box 86)
    - Citywide Recreation Survey, 1961 (Box 86)
  - Departments, mayors, Division of Neighborhood Improvement (Box 87)
  - Division of Neighborhood Improvement, environmental sanitation (Box 88)
  - Environmental sanitation, ordinances (Box 89)
  - Ordinances, human relations, human rights, commercial projects (Box 90)
  - Commercial projects (Box 91)
  - Commercial projects, demolition, disposition (Box 92)
  - Disposition, city programs/projects (Box 93)
  - City programs/projects, city schools (Box 94)
  - City schools (Box 95)
  - City schools, agencies/institutions/universities (Box 96)
  - Agencies/institutions/universities (Box 97–100)
- Contracts and Agreements, Series VII
  - 8-1 Oak Street (Box 101)
  - R-1 Wooster Square (Box 101)
  - R-1 Wooster Square (Box 102)
  - 8-1 Oak Street (Box 102)
  - R-2 Church Street (Box 102)
  - R-2 Church Street (Box 103)
  - R-2 Church Street (Box 104)
  - R-20 Dixwell Avenue (Box 105)
  - R-20 Dixwell Avenue (Box 106)
  - R-28 State Street (Box 106)
  - R-28 State Street (Box 107)
  - R-71 Dwight Street (Box 107)
  - R-71 Dwight Street (Box 108)
  - R-79 Fair Haven (Box 108)
  - R-79 Fair Haven (Box 109)
  - R-79 Fair Haven (Box 110)
  - R-82 Hill High School (Box 110)
  - R-91 Newhallville (Box 111)
  - R-96 Hill (Box 111)
  - R-96 Hill (Box 112)
  - R-106 Temple George (Box 112)
  - Long Wharf (Box 112)
  - Long Wharf (Box 113)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 113)
  - R-48 (Box 113)
  - Community renewal program (Box 113)
  - Neighborhood development program (Box 114)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 115–119)
- Demolition/Contracts, Series VIII
  - All projects (Box 120)
  - General (Box 120)
  - 8-1 Oak Street (Box 120)
  - 8-1 Oak Street (Box 121)
  - R-2 Church Street (Box 121)
  - R-1 Wooster Square (Box 121)
  - R-2 Church Street (Box 122)
  - R-1 Wooster Square (Box 122)
  - R-1Wooster Square (Box 123)
  - R-1 [Wooster Square] and R-2 [Church Street] (Box 123)
  - 8-1 Oak Street (Box 124)
  - R-2 Church Street (Box 124)
  - R-1 Wooster Square (Box 124)
  - R-1 Wooster Square (Box 125)
  - R-2 Church Street (Box 125)
  - R-20 Dixwell Avenue (Box 126)
  - R-1 Wooster Square (Box 126)
  - R-2 Church Street (Box 126)
  - R-2 Church Street (Box 127)
  - R-20 Dixwell Avenue (Box 127)
  - R-71 Dwight Street (Box 127)
  - R-82 Hill High School (Box 127)
  - R-1 Wooster Square (Box 127)
  - R-79 Fair Haven (Box 127)
  - R-2 Church Street (Box 128)
  - R-20 State Street (Box 128)
  - R-71 Dwight Street (Box 128)
  - R-1 Wooster Square (Box 128)
  - R-79 Fair Haven (Box 128)
  - R-91 Newhallville (Box 128)
  - R-28 State Street (Box 128)
  - R-1 - R-96 Wooster Square-Hill Project (Box 129)
  - R-1 - R-96 Wooster Square - Hill Project (Box 130)
  - Long Wharf (Box 130)
  - R-1 - R-96 Wooster Square-Hill Project (Box 130)
  - A-8-1 - A-8-2 (Box 131)
  - R-1 - R-106 Wooster Square-Temple Street Garage (Box 131)
  - BE-1 (Box 131)
  - PA-1 (Box 131)
- Development Administrator's Files, 1980-1985; Series IX
  - Affirmative action, airport, Air Rights Garage (Box 132)
  - Air Rights Garage, Aldermen, Board of; Assessor, Office of (Box 133)
  - Audubon Street reconstruction, building inspection, Chapel Square Mall (Box 134)
  - Charter revision commission, city bank program, city engineer, city hall court case, city point development (Box 135)
  - City vehicles, community development (Box 136)
  - Community development, Connecticut Conference of Municipalities, Connecticut Limousine (Box 137)
  - Connecticut Resources Recovery Authority, Council for Urban Economic Development, Development administration correspondence (1981) (Box 138)
  - Department of Transportation, development administration, Dixwell Community House, downtown, East Haven Industrial Park (Box 139)
  - Economic development, education, finance, board of, Gateway landing (Box 140)
  - Giordano housing proposal, Goals for New Haven Planning Commission, Heritage Hall, housing authority, housing sites (Box 141)
  - Housing task force, labor relations, legislation, Mayor's Education Management Task Force (Box 142)
  - Media council, neighborhood preservation, North Haven mall (Box 143)
  - North Haven mall, northeast corridor (Box 144)
  - Olin Science Park, parking authority, parks and recreation, preservation trust, Public Works Department (Box 145)
  - Purchasing Department; recycling; Redevelopment Agency; Regional Planning, Agency of South Central Connecticut; Rouse (Box 146)
  - Route 34, sewer agreements, East Short WPAP electric claim (Box 147)
  - Sewer facilities plan (Box 148)
  - Sewer fund, Shubert Theater (Box 149)
  - Connecticut Resources Recovery Authority, Small Business Administration, tax abatement program, traffic and parking, tri-centennial (Box 150)
  - Transition, Urban Development Action Grants, upper Chapel, upper State, Urban League (Box 151)
  - Urban Reinvestment Task Force, utilities, water pollution, Westville, Whalley Avenue Businessmen's Association, Whitney-Grove, Yale New Haven Hospital, zoning (Box 152)
  - Administration-commercial revitalization (Box 153)
  - Commercial revitalization-departments (Box 154)
  - Departments-downtown harbor (Box 155)
  - General - legislative (Box 156)
  - Legislative - Whitney Grove, and loose materials (Box 157)
- Environmental Impact, Series X
  - Correspondence (Box 158)
  - Air (Box 158)
  - Census (Box 158)
  - Climate (Box 158)
  - ECO (Box 158)
  - ECO (Box 159)
  - Environmental Council-city (Box 159)
  - Environmental impact statements (Box 159)
  - Environmental impact statements (Box 160)
  - Environmental legislation (Box 160)
  - General Connecticut (Box 160)
  - General New Haven (Box 160)
  - Historical sites (Box 160)
  - Newsletters-magazines (Box 160)
  - Maps (Box 160)
  - Public opinion (Box 160)
  - Sewers (Box 160)
  - Sewage treatment (Box 161)
  - Noise (Box 161)
  - Transportation (Box 161)
  - Soil (Box 161)
  - Social environment (Box 161)
  - Solid waste (Box 161)
  - Utilities (Box 161)
  - Vegetation (Box 162)
  - Water ways (Box 162)
  - Wetlands (Box 162)
  - Wildlife (Box 162)
- Federal Government, Series XI
  - Legislation (Box 163)
  - Legislation (Box 164)
  - Federal National Mortgage Association-FHA (Box 165)
  - Community Facilities Administrator [CFA] (Box 165)
  - HUD-Urban Renewal Administration [URA] (Box 166–169)
  - Federal programs (Box 170, Box 172)
- Housing Code Compliances, Series XII
  - Lyon Street-Market Street (Box 173)
  - 34 Market Street-177 Olive (Box 174)
  - Peck Street-231 Pine (Box 175)
  - Poplar-Rock Street (Box 176)
  - Saltonstall Avenue-862 1/2 State Street (Box 177)
  - 866 State Street-Willow Street (Box 178)
  - Wolcott-101 Woolsey (Box 179)
  - Wooster Street, files to be refiled [Cedar Hill-Wallace Street] (Box 180)
- Litigation, Closed Files, Series XIII
  - Advance Paper - Better Homes (Box 181)
  - Boccamaiello-Coles (Box 182)
  - College Plaza-Mackall (Box 183)
  - Mackall-New Haven Redevelopment Agency (Box 184)
  - New Haven Savings Bank-Pet-car Products (Box 185)
  - Property damage claims - Sykes (Box 186)
  - Taft-Zemel Bros. (Box 187)
  - Other cities
    - Bridgeport-Hartford (Box 187)
    - New Britain-Torrington (Box 188)
    - San Francisco (Box 188)
    - Trenton (Box 188)
- Office of Land Disposition, Series XIV
  - R-79 parcels [Fair Haven]
    - A-1 (Box 189)
    - S-3, S-4 (Box 189)
    - S-10 (Box 189)
    - S-9, S-11A, S-22, S-23, S31 (Box 189)
    - S-8 (Box 189)
    - S-14 (Box 189)
    - C-1 (Box 190)
    - S-27 (Box 190)
    - S-28, S-29, S-30 (Box 190)
    - S-32 (Box 190)
    - S-32A (Box 190)
    - S-32B (Box 191)
    - S-32A (Box 191)
  - R-91 Parcels [Newhallville]
    - A-2 (Box 191)
    - A-3A (Box 191)
  - R-96 Hill Project, Port Sea Street, 267-269, 271-277, 279-281 (Box 192)
  - R-91 Parcels [Newhallville]
    - S-3A (Box 192)
    - S-3C (Box 192)
    - S-5 (Box 192)
    - S-6 (Box 192)
    - S-7 (Box 193)
    - S-9 (Box 193)
    - S-10 (Box 193)
    - S-12 (Box 193)
    - S-15 (Box 193)
    - S-16A (Box 193)
    - S-22 (Box 193)
    - S-23 (Box 193)
    - S-24 (Box 194)
  - Wilmot Road, Parcel 2A (Box 194)
  - R-106 Temple George, Parcel A-1 (Box 194)
  - R-96 Parcels [Hill Project]
    - S-41 (Box 194)
    - S-34 (Box 194)
    - S-35 (Box 194)
    - S-36 (Box 194)
    - S-38 (Box 194)
    - S-40 (Box 194)
  - Long Wharf, Seamless Rubber Company (Box 195)
  - R-96 Parcel S-26 [Hill Project] (Box 195)
  - Long Wharf parcels
    - B-1 (Box 195)
    - B-3 (Box 195)
    - A (Box 195)
    - B-2-B (Box 195)
    - D (Box 195)
    - B, B-1, and C (Box 196)
    - B-3 (Box 196)
    - B-3-B (Box 196)
    - B-3 (Box 196)
    - B-3 (Box 197)
    - Block E (Box 197)
    - G-1 (Box 197)
    - G-1, H, H-1 (Box 197)
    - L, option parcels 1 and 2 (Box 197)
    - SA-1 (Box 197)
    - SA-1 (Box 198)
    - E (Box 198)
    - S-A-2 (Box 198)
  - R-96 parcels [Hill Project]
    - A-3-C (Box 199)
    - A-3-D (Box 199)
    - A-3-E (Box 199)
    - A-3-F (Box 199)
    - S-24 (Box 199)
    - A-3-A (Box 199)
    - A-3-F-A (Box 200)
    - B-1-B (Box 200)
    - B-2-B (Box 200)
  - R-2 Blocks Aand B [Church Street] (Box 200)
  - Stevens-Malley-Yale recorded documents (Box 200)
  - R-2 Parcel 1-A [Church Street] (Box 200)
  - R-2 Blocks [Church Street]
    - A and B (Box 201)
    - A, B, C, D (Box 201)
    - C (Box 201)
    - C (Box 201)
    - D (Box 201)
    - H (Box 201)
    - R. H. Macy and Company (Box 201)
    - D (Box 201)
    - G (Box 202)
  - R-2 parcel 1-A [Church Street] (Box 202)
  - R-2 Block J [Church Street] (Box 202)
  - R-2 new house site #1E [Church Street] (Box 202)
  - R-2 new house site #2J [Church Street] (Box 202)
  - R-2 new house site #3L [Church Street] (Box 202)
  - R-2 parcels [Church Street]
    - D (Box 203)
    - G (Box 203)
    - H (Box 203)
    - I (Box 203)
    - K (Box 203)
    - M (Box 203)
    - M (Box 204)
    - O (Box 204)
    - R-2 (Box 204)
    - Q-R-1 addition (Box 204)
    - Q-R-1 (Box 204)
  - R-20 parcels [Dixwell]
    - 1A, 1B, 1C, 1D (Box 205)
    - S70 (Box 205)
    - 2-A (Box 205)
    - 2-B (Box 205)
    - 5 (Box 205)
    - S-21-A (Box 206)
    - S-22 (Box 206)
    - S-24 (Box 206)
    - S-25-A, S-37-B (Box 206)
    - S-25-B (Box 206)
    - S-31, S-32 (Box 206)
    - 6-B, 6-C (Box 206)
    - S-30 (Box 207)
    - S-26 (Box 207)
    - S-29 (Box 207)
    - S-35 (Box 207)
    - S-36 (Box 207)
    - S-38, S-39, S-40, S-49 (Box 208)
    - S-41 (Box 208)
    - S-42 (Box 208)
  - R-1 parcels [Wooster Square]
    - C-11-A (Box 209)
    - C-11-B (Box 209)
    - C-16 and C-17 (Box 209)
    - C-15-A (Box 209)
    - C-15-B (Box 210)
    - C-18 (Box 210)
    - C-19 (Box 210)
    - C-20-A (Box 210)
    - C-20-B (Box 210)
    - S-1 (Box 211)
    - S-2 (Box 211)
    - S-3 (Box 211)
    - S-3 (Box 211)
    - S-4 (Box 211)
    - S-5-B (Box 211)
    - S-8 (Box 211)
    - S-12-A (Box 211)
    - S-12-B (Box 211)
    - S-16-B (Box 211)
    - S-17-A (Box 211)
    - 15 Court Street (Box 212)
    - S-18-B (Box 212)
    - S-19-A-1, S-19-A-2 (Box 212)
    - S-21 (Box 212)
    - S-22-B (Box 212)
    - S-25 (Box 212)
    - S-26 (Box 213)
    - S-27-B (Box 213)
    - S-27-A (Box 213)
    - S-27-B (Box 213)
    - S-26 (Box 213)
    - S-27-C (Box 213)
    - S-28 (Box 214)
    - S-29 (Box 214)
    - S-30 (Box 214)
    - S-31-A (Box 214)
    - S-31-B (Box 214)
    - S-32-A (Box 214)
    - S-32-B (Box 214)
    - S-33 (Box 215)
    - S-34-A (Box 215)
    - S-35-A (Box 215)
    - S-36 (Box 215)
    - S-37 (Box 215)
    - S-38 (Box 216)
    - S-39 (Box 216)
    - 12 Court Street (Box 216)
    - 18 Court Street (Box 216)
    - 21 Court Street (Box 216)
    - 24 Court Street (Box 217)
    - 22 Court Street (Box 217)
    - 23 Court Street (Box 217)
    - 25 Court Street (Box 217)
    - 26 Court Street (Box 217)
    - 27 Court Street (Box 217)
    - 28 Court Street (Box 218)
    - 30 Court Street (Box 218)
    - 83 Olive Street (Box 218)
    - 93 Olive Street (Box 218)
    - Design files (Box 218)
    - A-6-B (Box 219)
    - A-6-C (Box 219)
    - A-7 (Box 219)
    - A-8 (Box 219)
    - A-11 (Box 219)
    - A-6-A (Box 219)
    - B-2-B (Box 220)
    - B-3 (Box 220)
    - B-4-B (Box 220)
    - B-5-A (Box 220)
    - B-5-B (Box 220)
    - B-6-A (Box 220)
    - B-6-B (Box 221)
    - B-7-B (Box 221)
    - B-7-A (Box 221)
    - B-7-A (Box 221)
    - B-9 (Box 221)
    - B-8 (Box 221)
    - B-10-B (Box 221)
    - B-12-A (Box 222)
    - B-12-B (Box 222)
    - B-15-B (Box 222)
    - B-12-D (Box 222)
    - B-12-E (Box 222)
    - B-12-F (Box 222)
    - B-12-G (Box 222)
    - B-12-G-2 (Box 223)
    - B-14-A (Box 223)
    - B-14-C (Box 223)
    - B-14-B (Box 223)
    - B-17 (Box 223)
    - B-13-B (Box 223)
    - B-18-A (Box 224)
    - B-18-C (Box 224)
    - B-19 (Box 224)
    - B-19 (Box 224)
    - C-1-A (Box 225)
    - C-1-D (Box 225)
    - C-1-H (Box 225)
    - C-1-B (Box 225)
    - C-1-J (Box 225)
    - C-1-K (Box 225)
    - C-1-L (Box 225)
    - C-1-M (Box 226)
    - C-1-N (Box 226)
    - C-1-O (Box 226)
    - C-1-P (Box 226)
    - C-1-P (Box 226)
    - C-1-R (Box 227)
    - C-3-A (Box 227)
    - C-2 (Box 227)
    - C-3 (Box 227)
    - C-4 (Box 227)
    - C-5, C-6-A, C-6-B, C-7-A, C-7-C, C-7-C (Box 228)
    - C-7-E, C-8-A, C-7-H, C-8-B, C-8-C, C-8-B, C-8-D, C-10 (Box 229)
  - 8-1 [Oak Street]
    - Parcel 2-A, 2-E (Box 230)
    - Parcels A, B, C (Box 230)
    - Lease between City of New Haven and University Towers (Box 230)
    - Parcels D, E (Box 230)
    - Crown Court (Box 230)
    - Block B (Box 230)
    - Parcels 4-E, 5-F (Box 231)
    - Lease between City of New Haven and University Towers, Section B (Box 231)
    - Parcels I, G (Box 231)
  - R-20 [Dixwell]
    - Parcels S-43, S-44-B, S-44-C, S-47-A, S-47-B, S-51, S-52, S-53, S-54 (Box 232)
    - Parcels S-55-A, S-55-B, S-58, S-59, S-60-A, S-63 (Box 233)
    - Parcels S-64, S-67, S-71, S-72, S-77 (Box 234)
    - Parcel S-78 (Box 235)
  - R-28 Parcels [State Street]
    - A-6, I-1, I-2, E (Box 235)
    - E-2, E-3, E-4, A-3-A, A-1 (Box 236)
  - R-71 Parcels [Dwight]
    - A-1, A-2-A, A-6, A-2-B, A-3-A, S-6-A, S-6-B (Box 237)
    - B-2-A, A-7-C, A-6-A, A-7-A (Box 238)
    - A-7-E, A-7-F, A-7-H, A-7-G (Box 239)
    - A-7-J-A, B-2-B, A-7-J, A-7-K, A-7-L, A-7-A, A-7-D, A-7-B, B-2-A (Box 240)
    - B-2-B, B-2-B addition, S-1, S-2-B, S-3-B, S-3-A, S-4 (Box 241)
    - S-5-D, S-5-A, S-7-A, s-7-B, S-8 (Box 242)
    - S-9, S-10, S-12, S-14 (Box 243)
    - S-16-A, S-16-B, S-16-C, S-16-D, S-16-E, S-16-F, S-17, 410 Orchard Street (Box 244)
- Office of Public Information, Series XV
  - Vertical File
    - Misc (Box 245–246)
    - Staff biographies, articles (Box 247)
    - Articles, New Haven firms and articles (Box 248)
    - New Haven articles (Box 249)
    - Articles (Box 250)
    - Police (Box 251)
    - Festivals (Box 251)
  - Fact Sheets
    - Air Rights Garage -Seamco (Box 252)
    - Shartenberg -Robert T. Wolfe Apartments (Box 253)
    - Art and Architecture -Crawford Manor (Box 253)
    - Dewitt Jones -Lehman and Harrison (Box 254)
    - Liberty Square homes -SNET company building (Box 255)
    - SNET Court Street building -Winter Gardens (Box 256)
  - Contact sheets and prints (Box 257–259)
  - Subject files
    - Advertising-agency press releases (Box 260)
    - Agency meetings (1977), brochures, miscellaneous (Box 261)
    - Budget-Church Street garage/Temple Park Plaza (Box 262)
    - Church Street (Box 263)
    - Church Street-City/Town development act (Box 264)
    - Code enforcement-community development (Box 265)
    - Community development-Community Progress Inc. (Box 266)
    - Community Progress Inc.-disturbances (Box 267)
    - Dixwell-drugs (Box 268)
    - Drugs-elderly (Box 269)
    - Elderly-Fair Haven (Box 270)
    - Fair Haven/Bella Vista-foreign trade zone study (Box 271)
    - Foreign trade zone study-halycon (Box 272)
    - Harbor-hill (Box 273)
    - Lee High School-housing (Box 274)
    - Housing-legal aid (Box 275)
    - Light Switch Liquors-model cities (Box 276)
    - Model cities-Newhallville (Box 277)
    - Newhallville-parks (Box 278)
    - Parks-research program (Box 279)
    - Pollution-Route 34 (Box 280)
    - Parks-State Street (Box 281)
    - State Street (Box 282)
    - State Street-summer programs (Box 283)
    - Summer programs - transportation (Box 284)
    - Traffic-United Illumination (Box 285)
    - Veterans-Wooster Square (Box 286)
    - Wooster Square-Yale, miscellaneous (Box 287)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 288–294)
    - Mayor's redevelopment files (Box 295–298)
    - Mayoralty contests, 1969-1977 (Box 299)
    - Audio [masters only] (Box 300)
      Conditions Governing Access